{
  "current": "11",
  "1": {
    "question": "\u0421\u0442\u043e\u043b\u0438\u0446\u0430 \u0413\u0440\u0435\u0446\u0438\u0438?",
    "answers": [
      "\u0410\u0444\u0438\u043d\u044b",
      "\u0421\u0442\u0430\u043c\u0431\u0443\u043b",
      "\u0421\u0430\u043b\u043e\u043d\u0438\u043a\u0438",
      "\u0418\u0440\u0430\u043a\u043b\u0438\u043e\u043d"
    ],
    "right_answer": "\u0410\u0444\u0438\u043d\u044b",
    "right_answer_id": "a"
  },
  "2": {
    "question": "\u0421\u043a\u043e\u043b\u044c\u043a\u043e \u043b\u044e\u0434\u0435\u0439 \u0436\u0438\u0432\u0451\u0442 \u0432 \u0413\u0440\u0435\u0446\u0438\u0438?",
    "right_answer": "10,27 \u043c\u043b\u043d",
    "right_answer_id": "d",
    "answers": [
      "8,5 \u043c\u043b\u043d",
      "12,3 \u043c\u043b\u043d",
      "9,7 \u043c\u043b\u043d",
      "10,27 \u043c\u043b\u043d"
    ]
  },
  "3": {
    "question": "\u042d\u043a\u0437\u043e\u0442\u0438\u0447\u0435\u0441\u043a\u0438\u0439 \u0433\u043e\u0440\u043d\u044b\u0439 \u0442\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0441\u043f\u043e\u0440\u0442?",
    "right_answer": "\u041e\u0441\u0451\u043b",
    "right_answer_id": "a",
    "answers": [
      "\u041e\u0441\u0451\u043b",
      "\u041b\u0430\u043c\u0430",
      "\u0412\u0435\u0440\u0431\u043b\u044e\u0434",
      "\u042f\u043a"
    ]
  },
  "4": {
    "question": "\u041d\u0430\u0446\u0438\u043e\u043d\u0430\u043b\u044c\u043d\u0430\u044f \u0432\u0430\u043b\u044e\u0442\u0430 \u0413\u0440\u0435\u0446\u0438\u0438 \u0434\u043e \u0415\u0432\u0440\u043e?",
    "right_answer": "\u0413\u0440\u0435\u0447\u0435\u0441\u043a\u0430\u044f \u0434\u0440\u0430\u0445\u043c\u0430",
    "right_answer_id": "c",
    "answers": [
      "\u0413\u0440\u0435\u0447\u0435\u0441\u043a\u0438\u0439 \u043b\u0435\u0439",
      "\u0413\u0440\u0435\u0447\u0435\u0441\u043a\u0438\u0439 \u0444\u0440\u0430\u043d\u043a",
      "\u0413\u0440\u0435\u0447\u0435\u0441\u043a\u0430\u044f \u0434\u0440\u0430\u0445\u043c\u0430",
      "\u0413\u0440\u0435\u0447\u0435\u0441\u043a\u0438\u0439 \u0434\u043e\u043b\u043b\u0430\u0440"
    ]
  },
  "5": {
    "question": "\u041e\u0442\u0435\u0446 \u0417\u0435\u0432\u0441\u0430, \u0410\u0438\u0434\u0430, \u041f\u043e\u0441\u0435\u0439\u0434\u043e\u043d\u0430?",
    "right_answer": "\u041a\u0440\u043e\u043d\u043e\u0441",
    "right_answer_id": "d",
    "answers": [
      "\u0423\u0440\u0430\u043d",
      "\u0413\u0435\u044f",
      "\u0422\u0438\u0442\u0430\u043d",
      "\u041a\u0440\u043e\u043d\u043e\u0441"
    ]
  },
  "6": {
    "question": "\u041a\u0430\u043a\u0430\u044f \u0441\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043d\u044f\u044f \u0442\u0435\u043c\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0430\u0442\u0443\u0440\u0430 \u0438\u044e\u043b\u044f?",
    "right_answer": "33",
    "right_answer_id": "b",
    "answers": [
      "28",
      "33",
      "36",
      "30"
    ]
  },
  "7": {
    "question": "\u0421\u043a\u043e\u043b\u044c\u043a\u043e \u043e\u0441\u0442\u0440\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0432 \u043f\u0440\u0438\u043d\u0430\u0434\u043b\u0435\u0436\u0438\u0442 \u0413\u0440\u0435\u0446\u0438\u0438?",
    "right_answer": "2000",
    "right_answer_id": "c",
    "answers": [
      "1500",
      "2500",
      "2000",
      "3000"
    ]
  },
  "8": {
    "question": "\u041a\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0439 \u043f\u0440\u0438\u0440\u043e\u0441\u0442 \u043d\u0430\u0441\u0435\u043b\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f \u0432 \u0413\u0440\u0435\u0446\u0438\u0438?",
    "right_answer": "-0.4%",
    "right_answer_id": "d",
    "answers": [
      "0.2%",
      "0.1%",
      "0.3%",
      "-0.4%"
    ]
  },
  "9": {
    "question": "\u041a\u0430\u043a \u043d\u0430\u0437\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0441\u0430\u043c\u043e\u0435 \u043a\u0440\u0443\u043f\u043d\u043e\u0435 \u043a\u0430\u0440\u0441\u0442\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0435 \u043e\u0437\u0435\u0440\u043e \u0413\u0440\u0435\u0446\u0438\u0438?",
    "right_answer": "\u042f\u043d\u0438\u043d\u0430",
    "right_answer_id": "c",
    "answers": [
      "\u041f\u0430\u043c\u0432\u043e\u0442\u0438\u0434\u0430",
      "\u0422\u0440\u0438\u0445\u043e\u043d\u0438\u0434\u0430",
      "\u0412\u0435\u0433\u043e\u0440\u0438\u0442\u0438\u0434\u0430",
      "\u042f\u043d\u0438\u043d\u0430"
    ]
  },
  "10": {
    "question": "\u041a\u0430\u043a \u043d\u0430\u0437\u044b\u0432\u0430\u043b\u0430\u0441\u044c \u043a\u043d\u0438\u0433\u0430 \u0415\u0432\u043a\u043b\u0438\u0434\u0430 \u0441 \u0431\u0430\u0437\u043e\u0432\u044b\u043c\u0438 \u043f\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0443\u043b\u0430\u0442\u0430\u043c\u0438 \u0433\u0435\u043e\u043c\u0435\u0442\u0440\u0438\u0438?",
    "right_answer": "\u041d\u0430\u0447\u0430\u043b\u0430",
    "right_answer_id": "d",
    "answers": [
      "\u0413\u0435\u043e\u043c\u0435\u0442\u0440\u0438\u044f",
      "\u0422\u0435\u043e\u0440\u0435\u043c\u044b",
      "\u0410\u043a\u0441\u0438\u043e\u043c\u044b",
      "\u041d\u0430\u0447\u0430\u043b\u0430"
    ]
  }
}